{
    "subject": "resource/Laura_Love",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lincoln,_Nebraska",
    "human_readable": "Laura Love was born in Lincoln, Nebraska.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8475651144981384,
            "question": "Where was Laura Love born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7554248571395874,
            "question": "What year was Laura Love born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6477401256561279,
            "question": "Are there any famous people who were also born in Lincoln, Nebraska?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5503523945808411,
            "question": "What state is Lincoln, Nebraska in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3148868978023529,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Laura Love?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2707194685935974,
            "question": "Does Laura Love have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18474064767360687,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Lincoln, Nebraska?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1205589547753334,
            "question": "Is Lincoln a city or a state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08984586596488953,
            "question": "What is the capital of Nebraska?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08951832354068756,
            "question": "Is Lincoln a big city?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Laura Love was born in Lincoln, Nebraska.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8197_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the capital of Nebraska?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8197_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Lincoln a city or a state?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8197_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Lincoln, Nebraska?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8197_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8197_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, here is my evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while some documents mention Laura Love being born in Lincoln, Nebraska (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8197/re-ranker-msmarco/74.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8197/re-ranker-msmarco/105.txt), another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8197/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt) mentions that Laura was born in Guanajuato, M\u00e9xico."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Laura Love was born in Lincoln, Nebraska."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "At least three different sources (1, 2, 3) consistently report that Laura Love was born in Lincoln, Nebraska.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}